Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute, your smile.
可愛いですね、笑顔が
It's so cute!
め ちゃくちゃ可愛いですね
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
how are you?
元気ですか?
I'm fine.
元気です
Oh, how are you?
あ、元気?
yes.
はい
Ah, good.
あ、良かった
No, that's good.
いや、いいっすね
Small face.
顔ちっちゃ
happy.
嬉しい
It's about the size of one apple.
リンゴ1個分ぐらいですね
so.
こんなに
How old are you now?
今はいくつですか?
I'm 20 years old now.
今20歳です
Ah, you're young.
あ、若いですね
Pichi.
ピチピチの
Yes, I'm a fit 20 year old.
うん、ピチピチの20歳です
What do you usually do?
普段は何してるんですか?
Normally, I am currently accepting applications.
普段は、今は受付してます
of the company.
会社の
Ah, like a reception office.
あ、受付所みたいな
that's right.
そうです
You're working normally.
普通に働いてるんですね
Ah, that's good.
あ、良いっすね
If you go to a Ketsuke company and are greeted with a wonderful smile,
ケツケ会社行って、 素敵な笑顔で迎えられたら、
Looks like I'll be able to do my best for the day.
なんか1日頑張れそうですね
I would be happy if you could do that.
そうやってくれると、嬉しいです
That's a nice smile, really.
いい笑顔ですね、本当に
It's dazzling.
眩しいです
a little bit.
ちょっと
I need sunglasses.
サングラスが必要ですね
I'm embarrassed.
照れちゃう
Are you currently working at another job?
今は別の仕事してたんですか?
Before.
前は
I agree.
そうですね
Before, I was an idol in Akihabara.
前まではアイドルを秋葉原の方でやってました
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
yes.
はい
Hey.
へー
Ah, that's why.
あ、だからか
Is that why?
だからかってか
There's something a little idol-like about her.
ちょっとアイドルっぽいところありますよね
I agree.
そうですね
I came here selling my smile.
笑顔を売りにしてやってきたので
Also with the fans.
ファンの方ともね
But I feel a little lonely,
でもちょっと寂しくなっちゃうので、
I quit being an idol and am now working as an asshole.
アイドルの方はやめて、今はケツケの仕事してます
What makes you feel lonely?
寂しくなっちゃうっていうのは何がですか?
The fans are leaving us,
ファンの方が離れていっちゃうっていうのが、
Because I'm lonely.
寂しいので
Ah, the people who were fans are leaving.
あ、ファンだった人が離れていくのが、
Are you feeling a little lonely?
ちょっと寂しくなっちゃったんですか?
I agree.
そうだね
Ah, this is such a sad league.
あ、なんかすごい切ないリーグですね
painful.
切ない
It's sad.
切ないね
That was a little tough, that's for sure.
それがちょっときつかった、確かに
You can't be an idol.
アイドルできないよね
It's not like they're supporting me all the time.
ずっと応援してくれてるわけでもないもんね
I'm still working as a receptionist, but I'm also interested in becoming an actress.
今も受付やってて、でもちょっと女優とかの方も興味がある
Or rather, I thought that I would like to become an actress as well.
っていう か、 女優の方もやりたいなと思って、
I'm thinking about it now.
今考えています
Ah, at first I felt like I really wanted to go into the entertainment industry.
あ、最初でやっぱり芸能界に行きたいみたいな思いが
Eh, I can go.
え、行けるっすよ
I'll take a look.
ちょっと見るよ
I want you to do your best.
頑張ってほしい
amazing.
すごい
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏さんいたりします?
My boyfriend isn't here right now.
今いないですね、彼氏は
Oh, he's not there.
あ、いないんだ
When was the last time you were there?
最後にいたのはいつですか?
The last time I was there was probably about 5 months ago.
最後にいたのもう5ヶ月ぐらい前かな
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Why was it divided?
それは分かれちゃった理由は?
The reason why we split up.
分かれちゃった理由
We were living far away, so I thought it would be a little difficult.
遠距離してて、それでちょっと難しいなと思っちゃって、
As for long distance.
遠距離は
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Because I can't meet you soon.
すぐに会えないから
That's right.
そうなんだ
I agree.
そうですね
Was long distance still difficult?
遠距離やっぱりきつかった?
How long have you been away today?
今日どんぐらい離れてたんですか?
It was mostly Aichi and Tokyo.
どんぐらい、愛知と東京でした
Can't meet often?
なかなか会えない?
Yeah, I couldn't meet you right away.
うん、すぐには会えないかったです
Is it hard not being able to see you?
会えないのがつらい?
Yeah, it's tough.
うん、つらいです
Have you been in touch?
連絡はしてた?
every day.
毎日
Yeah, every day.
うん、毎日
It's LINE though.
LINEですけど
But there were also quite a few telephone calls.
でも電話も結構ありました
But it makes me want to meet you.
でも会いたくなっちゃうよね
Yeah.
うん
It's really hard when you get lonely.
寂しくなるとやっぱつらいもんね
It's cute.
かわいいね
So, he's not there now.
で、今はいないんですね
That's right.
そうなんです
It's a bit of a naughty story.
ちょっとウエッチな話なんですけど
How many people need experience?
経験ニーズとかって、何人くらいなんですか?
Two people need experience.
経験ニーズは2人ですね
lie!?
嘘!?
Only 2 people.
2人だけ
Is that without any fans?
それはファンの人はいれずに?
Yeah.
うん
It doesn't help the fans.
ファンの人には手伝わらない
Won't you help me?
手伝わらない?
That's right.
そうだよね
Does that include the long-distance boyfriend you were dating?
それはその付き合ってた遠距離の彼を含めてってこと?
That's right.
そうなんです
Well, that's how it is.
まあでもそんなもんだよね
Have you ever been photographed like this before?
こうやって撮られたりするのはありました今まで?
I didn't talk a lot about myself.
自分のことをいっぱい喋るっていうのはなかったですね
TRUE?
本当?
I see.
そうか
You're used to it because you were an idol, right?
アイドルやってたから慣れてるでしょ?
I guess I'm not used to that.
そんな慣れてないんですね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I thought I'd take a photo of the depths of that smile today.
ちょっと今日はその笑顔の奥の奥まで撮っちゃおうかなと思って
Deep inside?
奥の奥まで?
Specially?
特別に?
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's cute.
かわいいですね
Her dimples are so cute.
えくぼがめちゃくちゃかわいい
He's charming when he smiles.
笑った時のここがチャーミングだね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you told?
言われる?
often.
よく
It's said sometimes.
たまに言われます
Dimples are love holes.
えくぼは恋の年穴だね
Well, dimples are love holes.
そうですね、えくぼは恋の年穴
Can I ask you to say something cute?
ちょっとかわいらしく言ってもらっていいですか?
Dimples are love holes.
えくぼは恋の年穴
cute?
か わいい?
amazing.
すごい
Did you say that?
それ言ってた?
Didn't you say that?
言ってなかった?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいですね
It tastes sweet.
甘い味がするね
Sweet taste.
甘い味が
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Stick your tongue out a little.
ちょっと舌出して
It gives you a really rich air.
すっごい濃厚な宙をしてくれるんだね
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
It's cute.
かわいいね
Has it been a while since you did something like this?
こういうことするのは久々ですか?
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
Has it been a while?
久しぶりですか?
Don't worry about the door.
ドアがあるのは気にしないで
It is the door to the future.
未来への扉です
Feel like opening it?
開けたくなった?
I wanted to open it.
開けたくなった
So, can I open this door of hope?
じゃあ、この希望の扉を開けていいですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's hope for me.
俺にとって希望なんで
There's super cute clothes in there.
超かわいい人着入ってる
So cute.
すげーかわいい
Are you hiding something?
何か隠すの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Cute clothes.
かわいい人着
Can fans see it?
ファンの人は見れると?
He's a man you shouldn't look at.
見ちゃダメな男です
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
No?
ダメ?
Don't look at it.
見ちゃダメ
I just flipped through it a little.
ちょっとめくっちゃったんだけどさ
show me.
見せて
By yourself.
自分で
That's right.
そうだよ
Because it was cute.
可愛かったから
oh.
おお
I don't really understand the concept of minimalism.
ミニマムさがさあ、あんまわかんないと思うんだよね
Oh, that's amazing.
おお、すごい
The style is really nice.
スタイルめっちゃいいね
Great style.
すごいスタイルいい
nice.
いいね
cute.
かわいい
Were you wearing a swimsuit?
水着になったりしてた?
When Idol.
アイドルの時
Just a little bit.
ちょこっとだけ
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
Well, there's still plenty of time.
じゃあ、まだ余裕だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですよ
real?
ほ んと?
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみて
behind.
後ろ
It's just a little bit.
ちょこちょこちょこちょこですね
Yes, show me your butt.
はい、お尻見せて
oh yeah.
そうそう
You look so erotic.
めちゃくちゃエロい格好してるね
Did you pose like this?
こういうポーズはしてたの?
No, I don't really do it.
いや、なかなかしない
This is a gravure idol.
これはグラビアアイドルなんだね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
But it's super cute.
でも、超かわいい
That's great.
すげーいいね
Your butt is beautiful.
お尻きれいだね
There are stains.
しみができてるよ
Have you ever worn a thong?
Tバックとか履いたことある?
No, thong.
ないです、Tバック
do not have?
ない?
do not have.
ない
It's really soaked though.
すっごいぐしょぐしょになってるけど
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
That's amazing.
すごいよ
I find it easy to paint.
私、塗りやすい
yes.
はい
You look like a half-Japanese.
ハーフみたいな顔してるね
Isn't that often said?
よく言われないですか?
It's said sometimes.
たまに言われます
Ah, you say that.
あ、言われますよね
Well then, huh?
じゃあ、 ん?
When?
いつの間に?
yeah?
ん?
It had been taken.
取られてたの
can be?
あり?
why?
なんで?
Why?
どうして?
It's delicious.
うまいね
Oh, it was so nice to go, right?
あ、 すっとこう、 行くのがうまかったっすね、
now.
今
professional.
プロ
Looks like a pro.
プロみたい
Are you a professional?
プロなの?
Not a professional.
プロじゃない
Indeed, when I was wearing a swimsuit, the photographer forced me to take it off.
確かに、これ水着の時にね、カメラマンに 無理やり剥がされる
Because it might happen.
こと あるかもしれないからね
Flicker flicker.
チラチラチラチラ
I can see it.
見えてるよ
A sneak peek.
チラ
Did you give me a glimpse?
チラしてくれたの?
You're so kind.
優しいね
Did you give me a glimpse?
チラしてくれたの?
Super beautiful.
超綺麗
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だね
Super soft.
超柔らかい
Is it more open?
もっと開いてるのか
Is it open?
開いてるの?
Wow, it's delicious.
すげえ、おいしい
delicious.
おい しい
It tastes like banana.
バナナの味がする
Banana flavor.
バナナの味
why?
なんで?
Because I'm eating a lot of bananas.
バナナいっぱい食べてるから
amazing.
すごい
cute.
かわいい
It's really cute though.
めちゃくちゃかわいいんだけど
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hey, show me your legs.
ちょっとさ、脚見せて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's beautiful.
綺麗じゃん
It's smooth.
ツ ルツルだね
Chulchuru.
チュルチュル
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
You have a beautiful body, amazing.
綺麗な体だね、すごい
Come on, spread your legs.
ちょっとさ、足広げ
I understand that this is a naughty look.
これがやらしい格好っていうのが分か
Ru?
る?
Look, there's a stain.
ちょっと ほら、シミになってる
Stains.
シミ
Do you touch yourself here?
ここ自分で触ったりするの?
You thought about it for a while.
ちょっと考えたでしょ
I feel like I can't stand it anymore.
我慢できなくなる気がある
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I can smell it just in case.
一応匂い嗅いできます
He's a pervert.
変態さんだ
By now?
今頃?
He's a pervert.
変態さんだ
That's a beautiful face.
綺麗な顔だね
I ended up in the middle.
中んぼになっちゃったね
It's pink.
ピンク色だ
Wait, what is it?
ちょっと、なんだね
It's starting to grow.
生えかけてるんだね
I agree.
そうですね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Did you shave?
剃ってたの?
I was shaving.
剃ってました
I shaved it and it grew back.
剃ってて生えちゃったんだ
It has grown.
生えちゃいました
Are you tingling?
ヒクヒク寄せてる?
I haven't sent it.
寄せてない
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
すごい綺麗だよね、もう
You've never dressed up here, have you?
ここで格好したことないでしょ?
No.
ないです
Hey.
ねえ
That's no good.
だめだよね
Open it with your own hands and leave it there.
自分の手でさ、開いてからそのまま
It's pink.
ピンク色だね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Awesome.
すげえ
It's delicious.
美味しいよ
That's naughty, check this out too.
やらしいね、こっちも見て
That's naughty.
やらしい
It's really narrow.
すっごい狭いな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Amazing, tingling.
すごい、ヒクヒク
It was really tough though.
すげえキツイんだけど
Sorry.
ごめんね
Are you okay?
無事か
Was it tough?
キツイんですけ?
I don't know myself.
自分じゃわかんない
Are you told?
言われる?
I've been told this before.
言われたことはあります
be?
ある?
I feel like I'm going to break my finger.
指が折れそうだもん
Should I go home?
帰るかな?
But I like a little pain.
でもちょっと痛いの好きです
What does it mean to like pain?
痛いのが好きってどういうこと?
Do you mean a painful feeling?
痛い気持ちってこと?
being pushed out.
押し出される
But I'm being pushed out.
押し出されるんだけど
Are you pushing it out?
押し出してるでしょ?
I'm not pushing it out.
押し出してないよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Spread your legs.
足広げて
It's soaking wet.
びしょびしょになってるよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
It felt good.
気持ちよくて
It's out.
出ちゃったね
cute.
可愛い
It's so cute.
すげえ可愛いね
like?
好き?
I like it.
好きです
Seriously?
マジで?